it's
it is a good to have you all here
tonight and we're going to be covering
some there we go okay we're gonna be
covering a lot of material tonight but I
don't want you to be fearful because my
job tonight is to take some heavy
subjects and juice it down for you to
make it very simple so we're gonna be
looking at America in Bible prophecy
tonight now how many of you as you look
at what is going on in America today it
has you a little bit concerned okay you
know there are a lot of people that are
uncertain of the things that are
happening in our in our nation and where
this is all going and what I'm going to
share with you tonight is that what is
happening in America today what year are
we in we are in 2018 I'm gonna show you
that what is happening in America today
was foretold by the Year 95 ad almost
2,000 years ago the book of Revelation
was written or completed in 95 AD and
what we're going to see tonight is that
the book of Revelation over 2,000 years
ago foretold exactly where we are today
so we're gonna begin this presentation
and I'm gonna be sharing a couple things
we do now listen if if you are if this
is your first time opening a Bible is
your first time in a Bible seminar if
you're worried about how am I going to
understand this just be at ease because
I promise you you're going to understand
this and I'm gonna make it
so that
I'm gonna make sure that you are
following along with everything that I
say so that I will not leave anyone
behind okay all right so by the way does
anyone need a Bible if anyone needs a
Bible you you're not going to
necessarily need it tonight because
everything is on the screen so but if
you would like to have a Bible and you
do not have one just raise your hands
and we'll get it to you in the meantime
we're going to go ahead and begin this
presentation it's not going to be very
long we're going to try to get a lot of
material covered in a very in a short
time so here's a good news kind of good
news but bad news but good news here it
is what you're going to understand
tonight good news
millions are unaware of bad news okay
what you're going to understand tonight
is information that millions of people
are unaware of and I believe it is
absolutely crucial for them to be aware
so tonight you're in the right place
good news okay so there I am can you see
me
right there that's the guy okay
the name of the group boogie monsters
hip-hop group 1994 eighth album contract
with EMI records totaling a million
dollars skeptic of the Bible skeptic of
religion and then something happened and
that thing that happened led me to do
what I'm doing now walked away from that
contract have never looked back have
never said man maybe I made the wrong
decision this has become the consuming
passion of my life and I want to share
with you that that decision did not come
lightly growing up as a young person
growing up in New York City consider
myself very streetwise all religions are
man-made man wrote the Bible if you've
ever heard any of these things said by
people who don't believe in the Bible
that was me right oh the Bible was
written by man and bla bla bla
until someone showed me something and
I'm gonna share that with you tonight in
John chapter 14 verse 29 Jesus here
speaking says and now I have told you
before it come to pass that when it is
come to pass you might want Billy let me
explain that very quickly if I told you
fifty things that were going to happen
between tonight and next week you would
all probably think this guy's crazy but
if those 50 things happened in the order
in which I told you they were going to
happen
how many of you would begin to believe
that maybe there was something to what I
was saying
right because man does not have the
power to know the future man does have
so when Jesus here was speaking in the
Bible and he says listen I'm telling you
things that will come to pass before
they come to pass
that you might believe this is exactly
what he's saying no man has the power to
foretell the future right so if someone
foretells the future it is a sign that
it is something outside of human power
does that make sense so far all right
again the Bible tells us in Isaiah 41
verse 21 produce your cause save the
Lord bring forth your strong reasons
save the king of Jacob let them bring
them forth and show us what shall happen
let them show the former things what
they be that we may consider it and know
the latter end of them or declare unto
us things to come reading on so the
things that are to come here after that
we may know that ye are what God's ok
this is God here speaking according to
the Bible God is speaking through the
prophet Isaiah and what God does he says
listen tell the people to bring all
their gods together and whichever God
can tell you the future let that God be
God like that's God's challenge oh you
believe in what God okay how'd that God
tell you the future if that God can't
tell you the future he's not really he's
not really gone so God is claiming that
he is the only one that knows not only
the past but also the future and he says
I tell you the future so that you will
have no shadow of a doubt that I am real
so listen before the Christian I was
like you know you know how do we know
that this God / that God is real and you
know the people over there worship that
God and these people worship that God
you know who's to say which God is the
real God who's to say that there is any
gone and then when I saw this I was like
okay well if there was a God he would be
able to tell the future accurately
because no human can do that that's
something that is super natural and I'm
gonna share with you tonight that of all
the books on the planet there is only
one book that does that and does it
accurately and it is the Bible it is the
Bible I'm gonna show you that tonight
alright so we've set the founder
and now we're going to go into a
presentation there are three parts of
this presentation but fear not these
parts are going to be very brief because
we're going to start way way way in the
past and we're gonna work our way down
to this very date if I were to ask you
hey describe to me what's going on in
our nation today right would you pretty
much be able to give me a pretty
accurate description of the craziness
that is happening in our nation today
yeah I think everyone can do it right
there is a conflict in America right and
that conflict might be boil down to two
political parties all right the the what
we call the left and the right you guys
are brilliant you got it right so the
left and the right and and there's this
conflict on between the left and the
right that is tearing really tearing our
country apart you know I mean who knows
how this last Thanksgiving went when
people went home you know make sure you
do not talk about this thing right here
because it is so heated so let's see
what we're going to do is we're going to
go to the book of Revelation how many of
you've read the book of Revelation
before I maybe had difficulty
understanding the book of Revelation
right we're going to juice the book of
Revelation down and you're gonna see
some things that are going to be don't
like don't just smile be just don't fear
that I'm not gonna get this listen
you're gonna get this I promise you just
listen carefully to what I say all right
let's begin we're going to the book of
Revelation chapter 13 and in Revelation
chapter 13 verse 11 remember this book
was written in in what year he 195 ad
almost 2,000 years ago and in the book
revelation 13 verse 11 the Bible says
this is John the Revelator speaking he's
the one that wrote the book through the
inspiration of the Holy Spirit the Bible
says he relation 1311 I beheld another
what beast coming up out of the where
earth and he had two horns like a lamb
and he spoke as a dragon all right can
you imagine that in your mind do you see
that picture all right a beasts coming
about the earth two horns like a lamb
but speaks like a dragon so our question
is is this literal or symbolic now why
are we asking that question because no
one has ever seen a beast come up out of
the earth right
having horns like a lamb and speaking
like a dragon so common sense should
tell us that this is not something what
literal but it is Simba if it's not
literal it's got to be symbolic and that
makes sense okay
so close call beasts aren't because
aren't gonna be coming up out of the
earth at the end of time right no need
to be afraid like what was that this is
simply something symbolic now our next
question is does the Bible tell us then
how we should understand this symbolism
and the answer again is very simple
we're gonna go to another book in the
Bible the book of Daniel which is in the
Old Testament
Daniel is like the counterpart to the
book of Revelation Daniel was written
around 600 BC so that takes us even
further back in time but the prophet
Daniel said this in Daniel 7 verse 23
he's in the middle of a vision and an
angel tells him does he said the fourth
beast shall be the fourth what Kingdom
upon the earth which shall be diverse
from all kingdoms pause right there so
now we know that in the Bible a beast is
symbolic of a kingdom or a nation or a
power amen you got that so far so when
we go back to Revelation 13 and the
Bible says I saw a beast coming up out
the earth it is symbolic of saying I saw
a what nation rising into power if you
with me so far just nod your heads like
yes we're with you alright very good
okay so we see a beast equals a kingdom
excellent not
in Revelation 13 the very next verse it
says and he this beast that comes up out
of the earth with the horns of a land
speaks as a dragon exercise if all the
power of the first beast before him and
caused the earth and them that dwell
therein to worship the first beast whose
deadly wound was healed ok so what do we
what do we find out from this what do we
know what's the first thing we see here
there's another another beast ok another
beast that rolls before this beast with
the horns of a lamb that speaks like a
dragon all right so just make sure you
guys got this and we know so far that
there is a beast that has a horns of a
lamb speaks as a dragon but or this
beast or this kingdom or nation causes
others worship the Bible says the first
beast that came before him so what are
we looking for then we're looking for
another kingdom or nation so here's what
you want to do we want to get a little
bit more information about this first
beast because what all right focus now
which beast comes first
very good very the first beast comes
first all right now listen if you've
never studied the Bible before and some
of you may be here like oh the Bible's
just crazy but let me hear what this guy
has to say just hear me out is that okay
I'm wanting to show you even if you make
this may not believe in the Bible I'm
trying to give you a special key that
will help you to unlock the meaning of
the Bible so that it can at least make
sense and then you can say well I reject
this but at least it made sense are we
good
alright so we're gonna go back and learn
about this first beast the same book of
the Bible Revelation chapter 13 same
chapter in the first verse describes
this first beast okay now as you read in
this description you now know that there
is no need to be afraid because we know
that a beast simply represents a kingdom
all right so let's read revelation 13:1
I
upon the sand of the sea this is John
speaking and I saw a beast rising up out
of the sea having seven heads and ten
horns and upon his horns ten crowns and
upon his heads the name of blasphemy the
Beast which I saw was like unto a
leopard and his feet were as the feet of
a bear and his mouth as the mouth of a
lion and the dragon gave him his power
and seat and great Authority all right
so now we see this first beast being
described and give me the animals that
he looks like leopard bear lion dragon
all right those are the four animals
used to describe this Kingdom okay so
what we're gonna do cause we're like
okay who is this beast first of all we
don't know who any of these beasts yet
are doing no we just read about two
beasts and we know that they both
represent powers or kingdoms so what
we're gonna do is I'm gonna take you
back to the book of daniel which
describes this very same vision but
Daniel sees these four beasts as four
separate beasts John the Revelator saw
it as one but Daniel breaks it down for
us and breaks them down into four all
right so here's what it says in the Book
of Daniel Daniel spake and said I saw in
my vision by night and behold the four
winds of heaven strove upon the great
where was John when he saw this beast
sand of the sea and he sees the Beast
rising up out of the so we know ok this
kind of talking about the same thing
let's read on and four great beasts came
up from the sea diverse one from another
the first was like a hey does that ring
a bell anyone right not your head yes
Yeah right that rings a bell the first
was like a lion and behold another beast
a second like - a bear and the third
beast after this I beheld and lo another
like a wot leopard which had upon the
back of it four wings of a fowl the
Beast had also four heads interestingly
how many heads is that so far lion one
head bear one head this leopard has
four heads watch this after this I saw
in the night visions and behold a fourth
beast dreadful and terrible and strong
exceedingly and it had great iron teeth
and it was diverse from all the beasts
that were before it and it had ten horns
how many heads all together lion is one
bear is to the leopard has four so
that's six and then the fourth beast is
the seventh and then how many horns ten
horns so here's what we're seeing so far
hey pastor listen and Daniel Daniel is
telling us the same thing that John saw
beats with seven heads and ten horns but
again we have no idea who this power is
okay so we're trying to find out who
this power is well these four beasts you
see him again they're lion bear leopard
fourth beast dragon ten horns the Bible
tells us in Daniel 7 17 these great
beasts which are four are four kings
which shall arise out of the earth
now I'm gonna test you are you ready you
ready for that you didn't know you were
coming here to be tested tonight I'm
going to test you tell me the Beast
Beast number one lion followed by a
followed by a followed by a how many
horns ten horns very good excellent
excellent
so these four beasts the Bible says are
four kings that shall arise out of the
earth some translations say four
kingdoms so now the question is well who
do these kingdoms represent and the
answer is very simple you see when
Daniel was writing The Book of Daniel in
his time he was under his people the
Jewish people were captive to a power
named Babylon a king by the name of
Nebuchadnezzar now interestingly enough
the symbol for ancient Babylon was a
wind lion so here's what's happening
this lion in Daniel chapter 7 represents
that's a kingdom is it not yeah so
babylon babylon rules from 605 BC to 539
BC after the kingdom of Babylon another
kingdom came upon the scene that
overthrew Babylon that kingdom was the
medo-persian Empire so let me ask you
what beasts would represent the meat of
president Empire if the lion represents
Babylon then the bear would represent
medo-persia all right very good meter
person rule from 539 to 331 BC after
medo-persia medo-persia fell to another
power by the name of Greece the Grecian
kingdom Greece ruled from 331 BC to 168
BC now here's what's interesting who was
the ruler of Greece Alexander the Great
the Bible says this beast
remember this Daniel is writing in the
time of the Babylonian Empire he has no
way of knowing what's coming in the
future but he accurately predicts the
rise of medo-persia and then the rise of
Greece now the for the third beast this
leopard how many heads did it have four
heads do you know that when Alexander
the Great died his kingdom was divided
under four generals like how's that for
prophecy so here he has the kingdom
divided the Grecian Empire and now this
fourth beast what Kingdom overthrew
Greece the most famous ancient kingdom
in the world it was the Roman Empire
Rome ruled from 168 BC all the way to
476 ad all right now what does AD mean
what have we just done with ad we've
just come down to you know this side of
the timeline right no longer BC before
Christ ad we're now on our side of the
timeline so here's what just happened in
these four beasts the book of daniel has
just accurately predicted the rise four
kingdoms over a period of almost a
thousand
years so I'm gonna say Wow for you
Wow now now the Bible says that after
this Roman Empire after his fourth
kingdom the ten horns would rise out of
his kingdom those ten horns would
represent ten Kings or kingdoms and this
is after these ten Kings another king
was to arise and he will be different
from the first ones and shall subdue
three kings so there would be ten
kingdoms coming out of the Roman Empire
and then another kingdom would follow
those ten kingdoms out of Rome so did
that happen well remember I just said
that Rome fell in 476 ad when Rome fell
it was divided into into these kingdoms
see you there Alamein nah anglo-saxons
Burgundians Franks Caroline lombards
Ostrogoths wavey vandals bicycles ten
kingdoms that Rome was broken up too
broken up into when Rome fell all right
so what's happening here we're actually
moving down the timeline getting closer
to where we are today right so listen
the Bible says that after these ten
Kings another king was to arise it's in
Daniel 7:25 here it says this special
king this special king will say things
against God the most high and he will
hurt and kill God's special people
the king will try to change the times
and laws that have already been set
God's holy people will be under the
Kings power for 3 and 1/2 years okay so
we're told that a power listen carefully
power would rise out of what kingdom who
is a fourth beast Rome when Rome was
divided what and what had Rome do vaak
Rome divided became what we know today
as Europe
yeah so we're told that out of Europe
would arise a power after the front of
Rome that would persecute God's people
for three and a half years if you're
with me so far just shake your head we
got it okay so here's a question three
and a half years is that literal time or
symbolic time what do you think like if
the if if this whole book is symbolic
right meaning you've got to understand
what the symbols are then the time
should also be symbolic so now our
question is well if the time is symbolic
how do we know how we should apply three
and a half years by the way three and a
half years with equal 42 months 42
months with equal 1260 days listen
carefully the Bible tells us Bible tells
us in the Book of Ezekiel 4 verse 5 and
I'm just gonna read that last portion of
the verses this is God speaking I have a
pointed v each day for a year in bible
prophecy when time is symbolic that
means that a day would equal a a year
listen carefully guys because we're
coming down to something absolutely
amazing 1260 days would equal then 1260
years so now we're seeing that wherever
this power is it would persecute God's
people for 1260 years sometime after the
fall of the Roman Empire
if you're with me so far just nod your
head okay so when we take this angle
back to Revelation chapter 13 here's
what we see
about this first beast right the beast
that came before the Beast rising up out
of the sea out of the earth with the
horns of a lamb that same first beast is
described in this way there was given
him a mouth speaking great things and
blasphemies and power was given unto him
continue forty and two how long is that
that's three and a half years so what
did we just see what was written in
Daniel is the exact same thing that is
written in Revelation so we're checking
our work where we're looking and saying
okay we know that this is accurate
because what Daniel said is the same
thing that we're reading in the book of
Revelation that revelation sees it as
one beast where Daniel broke them up
into four beasts so here's a question it
goes on to save this of this beast he
opened his mouth and blasphemy against
God to blaspheme his name and his
tabernacle and then that dawn in heaven
and it was given unto him to make war
with the Saints and to overcome them and
power was given him over all Kindred's
tongues and nations so again this is
just verifying the Book of Daniel it's
telling us the same thing that the book
of Revelation chapter 13 is saying now
1260 days would equal 1260 years how
many of you ever heard a man by the name
of Constantine all right
Constantine was an emperor in Rome and
what Constantine did in around three
hundred and twenty three hundred ad
around that time is Constantine United
the the Christians with his empire he
actually converted to Christianity and
he made Christianity the state religion
he made Christianity what everyone okay
one more time he made Christianity what
everyone the state religion so check
this out whoa I'm about to excited sorry
sorry
Constantine unites church and state now
when that unification happened what
began what was the result that was that
as the state I'm sorry as the church
gained more power over the state
the church Christianity began to
exercise power that God had never put in
their hands did you catch that just now
so what happens is when Rome Falls in
476 ad another power would rise out of
Rome described as this 11th King if you
will and this King would dominate for
1260 years or a period known as the Dark
Ages which means if you take 1260 years
and you add it to that 500 you know the
5th century starting from 500 AD onward
it'll bring you down to the late 1700s
all right that's over 1,000 years of
persecution it's not a question for you
can you think can you think historically
speaking can you think of a group of
people that were responsible for
persecuting other people that did not
believe like they believed for a period
called the dark ages and let me answer
the question for you it is no other
power but the power of Christianity okay
that's crazy
because the Bible is supposed to uplift
Christians in the Bible Christians are
the good guys and the bad guys are those
people that don't believe in the Bible
but wait a minute the Bible actually
prophesied that there would be there
would be a people who would arise
claiming the name of Jesus and yet not
reflecting the character of Jesus let me
ask you do you know that most you know
one of the reasons why most people are
atheists most people are atheists
because of Christians
I don't know if you caught that just now
most people reject God because of what
they see Christians doing because if you
are to reflect this god that you say is
a God of love extension then how are you
acting like this
right so what God is pointing out here
in the Bible he's actually prophesying
he's saying listen our power is going to
rise that's going to claim to be serving
me but in actuality they're not serving
me so European Christianity what did
they do during those dark ages
they were persecuting power anyone ever
heard of the Spanish Inquisition yeah
all this is history and guess what guys
it lasted over 1,000 years just as the
Bible prophesied that it would this is
absolutely mind-blowing however it was
not all Christianity that was doing this
there were there was a remnant there
wasn't what everyone a remnant within
Christianity in other words while the
majority of Christians were living one
way and doing one thing and okay with
with with with persecuting there was a
small group of Christians that were not
doing and being hypocritical in their
faith mass Christianity gives God a bad
name during the dark ages okay how'd you
guys do we just finished part one are
you okay
everybody's still alive we're breathing
that wasn't that wasn't that like whoa I
know something I didn't know before
right okay so so part one took us from
you know 600 BC the rise of Babylon and
then medo-persia and then Greece and
Rome and then ten kingdoms rising out of
Rome then another Kingdom that dominates
for 1260 years bringing us down to the
end of the 1700s okay by the way
what happened to Christianity in the at
the end of the 1700s you're about to
find out next because that is part two
okay part two we're gonna be introduced
to another beast in the Bible now listen
I know that I'm going through things
rapidly well you may not know that but I
know that I'm going through things
rapidly because typically this would be
the kind of presentation that you take
like four weeks to do I'm giving you
like four weeks of stuff in like an hour
so you don't know that those so just
pretend I didn't say that okay so now
we're gonna look at another beast in the
book of Revelation and remember we're
trying to get to where we are when right
now today so we're gonna look at another
beast
another beast in the book of Revelation
and it's found in Revelation chapter 11
and I want you to know something here I
want you to recognize something anytime
you see 42 months 1260 days three and a
half years in prophecy you know we're
talking about the same time period are
you with me you same time period from
the far from 500 all the way down to the
end of the 1700s now watch this Bible
says in Revelation 11 1 and 2 there was
given me a reed like unto a rod and the
angel said stood saying rise and measure
the temple of God and the altar and them
that worship therein but the court which
is without the temple leave out and
measure it not for it is given unto the
Gentiles and the Holy City shall they
tread underfoot how long forty and two
months okay don't worry about anything
you just read except for that last line
how long forty and two months so here's
what I'm trying to tell you in
revelation 11 we know that we're being
introduced to the same time period all
right if you're with me so far give me a
nod okay now next verse revelation three
and I will give unto my two witnesses I
will give power unto my two witnesses
and they shall prophesy a thousand two
hundred and that word threescore it
means sixty in the Bible so 1260
days clothed in sackcloth is this the
same time period yeah so God here is now
saying hey during this time period of
1260 60 years I'm going to have two
witnesses prophesying now here's my
question to you these two witnesses are
they people why do we know they're not
people because nobody can leave no human
lives how long
want a soda these witnesses must be
symbolic are you with me so now again we
need to find okay in the Bible is there
anything that describes a witness
symbolically
and check this out Jesus himself said
these words can someone get me a bottle
of water please
thank you Jesus search the Scriptures
for in them you think you have eternal
life and these are they which one
testify what are the witness do a
witness testifies Jesus says here that
the Bible which is made up of Old
Testament and New Testament are his
witnesses I'm gonna tell you something
absolutely amazing do you know that
during the Dark Ages anyone that was
found with a Bible outside of the
priests were persecuted or even burned
at the stake you are not allowed to
possess a Bible therefore the Bible had
to do its work in secrecy
all right does that make sense the the
people who had the Bible who are trying
to get the light of the Bible out to
other people they had to do the work in
secrecy why because the priests in
Christianity would persecute they
believed that only they were able to
read and understand the Bible so anyone
who was impressed
of the Bible was considered a heretic
and was burned at the stake so the Bible
had to do its work for 1260 years in
hiding so to speak all right the Bible
says and when they shall finish their
testimony which would be when would they
finish their testimony that would be
around the end of the 1260 years so
we're looking for a round when the end
of the 1700s right when they shall have
finished their testimony the Beast that
ascendeth out of the bottomless pit
shall make war against them and shall
overcome them and kill them and their
dead bodies shall lie in the street of
that great city which is spiritually
called in Egypt where also was crucified
okay
a beasts question what is a beast in
Bible prophecy so we're looking for a
kingdom or a nation that would be coming
into some kind of power at the end of
when the 1700's listen carefully that
would be against the two witnesses who
are the two witnesses the Bible alright
guys I need you to think with me was
there a nation that at the end of the
1700s made an open war against the Bible
think think think think think some of
you know the answer be quiet I want you
to think was there a nation that at the
end of the 1700s made an all-out open
war on the Bible like had never happened
before in human history the answer is
yes the Bible says this place was
spiritually called Egypt and Sodom Egypt
in the Bible is known for its denial of
God Sodom was known for its lawlessness
so we're looking for a nation at the end
of 17
it's that anti-god and anti-bible
how many of you got that how many of you
are familiar with the French Revolution
do you know what happened the French
Revolution the French Revolution was a
revolt against Christianity you want to
know why because when France who was one
of the powers under the authority of
Christianity France got to a point where
they were so fed up with the hypocrisy
of Christianity that in the French
Revolution it was a revolt against
Christianity altogether they actually
outlawed for the first time ever in
human history God and the Bible were
outlawed like they actually in their
government like made a law that you
could not worship God that the Bible
could the Bible's all Bibles were to be
the burned or destroyed and this was in
reaction to hypocritical Christianity so
what do they do they de Christianized
friends they introduced secularism
atheism liberalism and in fact the
political terms left and right came out
of the French Revolution you are not
feeling me right now listen Napoleon in
1798 inflicted a devastating blow to
Christianity and I don't have time to go
into what that devastating blow our was
we will do that at some other time by
the way you are all handed these cards
as we're going through this study if
just look at that card it's it's simply
asking hey I'm intrigued and I want to
know more at any time you can fill this
card out and say yeah okay I need to
know more because guess what I'm not
covering everything tonight
okay so 160 years earlier
remember we said Napoleon inflicted this
this deadly blow to Christianity in 1798
twelve hundred and sixty years earlier
in 538 authority had been given to the
church to rule over all Kings the church
had been given authority to be the
highest ruler in Europe it was called
Justinian's decree and beloved that is
exactly 1260 years absolutely amazing
the French Revolution revolution the
French revolutionary term was where the
terms left-wing politics and right-wing
politics first originated the terms
arose from the seating of the ancient
regime of France at that time the
aristocrats sat on the right in other
words those who were in favor of the
church Jahna those who were in favor of
the church and thought that the church
should have dominion over the over the
state and father's should be no
separation of church and state those
were the ones that sat on the right of
the king while the commoners sat on the
left so the terms evolved to mean
involved to mean that the right wing
politics refer to politics for
aristocrats and royalty interest while
left-wing politics refer to
republicanism socialism and civil
liberties
are you thinking with me the Bible
prophesied this now now we just finished
part two how do you feel are you okay
yeah okay so watch this part 1 Babylon
medo-persia Greece Rome lion bear
leopard dragon ten horns divided Europe
power Rises out of divided Europe that
dominates for over 1,200 years that's
Christianity as a result of this
hypocritical Christianity France rejects
it rejects the Bible altogether and do
you know that atheism actually got its
rise out of the French Revolution before
that you could not spot an atheist out
in the open why because they'd be killed
by the church but in the French
Revolution we might in a sense say
people came out of the closet right yeah
we're open
atheists and you know what we reject God
and we reject the Bible and we're for
social liberties and we reject
Christianity in fact this is where the
term separation of church and state
found its meaning alright so here we go
now that that part 1 first beasts part 2
this beast from the abyss
so part 1 is the beast from the sea part
2 is the beast from the abyss and now
part 3 this is the conclusion because
we're trying to get down to where we are
right now and get ready I'm just I'm
just excited for you
watch watch part 3 is the beast from the
earth now in revelation 13:11 the verse
that we opened up with remember I saw I
beheld another beast coming up out of
the earth he had two horns like a lamb
and he spake as a dragon when John has
seen this at this time the first beast
has been wounded has recede
the deadly blow so in other words as
when this piece is coming up coming up
out of the earth it is just around the
time that the first beast had finished
his 1260 years of Dominion so we're
looking for a beast or a kingdom or
nation to rise up on the scene around
the same time that the first beast
received this wound around the same time
that France was was revolting pushing
their revolution this beast
the Bible says had horns like a lamb
all right so pastor okay
beast represents a nation but this beast
looks like a lamb so hmm what would that
symbolized I know why don't we ask the
question what does the lamb represent in
Scripture and here's what we find John
the Baptist said in John 1 and the next
day John seeth Jesus coming unto Him and
say it behold the which taketh away the
sins of the world so the lamb in the
Bible is symbolic of who Jesus so watch
this now here's what we can tell then we
are looking for a nation that would come
up on the scene around the end of the
1700s that would be what kind of a
nation a Christian nation a Christian
nation a Christian nation that would
rise up on the scene around the end of
the 1700 I wonder what power what nation
could that be
watch this guy's our Declaration of
Independence was signed in 1776 France
recognizes us independence in 1778 our
US Constitution is in effect by 1789 the
French Revolution begins in 1789
the Bill of Rights is added in 1791 and
Napoleon's army captures the Pope in
1798 listen can't watch this guy's beast
number one Christianity during the Dark
Ages beast number two the French
Revolution Beast number three the
American Revolution what all this is in
the Bible yet this is why I left a
million dollar contract behind this I
didn't walk away like I think I want to
be a Christian no no no no no no when I
saw this I was like what you mean God
knows the future God is real he actually
prophesied this before like this book
which is over 2,000 years old actually
contained this stuff that can be
verified by history whoa I have not I've
not seen any other quote unquote holy
book do this so now it had my interest
but watch this watch this
so the Bible says that though it had the
horns of a lamb it's fake like a one
dragon all right parsing can you imagine
like you know maybe going to the zoo one
day and you see a lamp and you want to
go up and pet the lamb right you go hi
little lamb and lamb W and goes wrong
how many of you would pass out would die
with right you don't expect a lamb to
roar like a dragon in the Bible the
dragon is symbolic of food we should all
know this the dragon is symbolic of
Satan so how can this nation which
claims to be lamb like right a Christian
nation
how
God described it as speaking like a
dragon well let me ask you something let
me let me ask you something let me ask
you something this nation claimed to be
founded upon what kind of principles
Christianity right all men some men some
men right I want you to think about this
now okay here's a nation that that
claimed we are God's nation God's people
and get that same nation from its
inception was speaking la like there is
no better description there is no better
description now listen watch this Casey
you think pasture are you you're talking
data listen not all Christians were like
the majority of Christians in this time
are you with me just like there was a
remnant during the dark ages guess what
in the end with the with the inception
of this nation there were godly men and
women who opposed what the nation the
Christian nation as a whole were doing
it that makes sense so this is not a a
condemnation of our nation okay there's
not a condemnation of all the people
that lived back in our time but I'm
simply showing you how accurate the
Bible was in actually describing this
nation as having horns of a lamb oh he's
so cute
but speaking like a dragon slavery I
want you to imagine what that must have
done to people struggling with
Christianity is the Bible really real is
God really a loving God well look at
those Christians who are selling people
look at those Christians and how there
wait oh wait a minute and you're saying
the Bible condones this oh and you're
using Bible verses to this day check
this out guys to this day atheists will
go to the Bible and will attempt to
prove that God actually was for slavery
and that's a whole nother subject but I
can guarantee you that God was not
condoning what they were doing that then
Christian nation horns of a lamb but
what spoke like a dragon all right so
listen to me guys this has nothing to do
with oh so the Bible is condemning right
people no all right and don't some of
you get happy like yeah no it's not what
the same don't do that
the Bible is condemning sin and guess
what all of us are guilty of sin all
right but I'm just showing you right now
listen we're just trying to see where
did we just came here tonight to find
out well what is going on in America but
we're getting a lot more than we brought
right we're seeing how this leads up so
watch this we're almost there
almost over almost finished so lamb
Christian nation
but dragon slavery so the Bible says
that this by the way not Rome to romans
2:24 for the name of god is blasphemed
among you among the Gentiles through you
as it is written you know that verse is
saying it was speaking to the Jews in
Christ's time but the Bible is saying
listen because of your inaccurate
portrayal of who God is the unbelievers
blaspheme God through your example this
is exactly what your just think about it
today what what does America you know
secular America think about Christianity
today just think about that just think
about that what do they think about
Christianity today about Christians
today okay we're moving on so two
revolutions French Revolution and the
American Revolution they both occur
at the same time what is a difference in
the revolutions one revolution rejected
Gong the left the other revolution
embraces God but under a dis under a
guise of hypocrisy the right are you
guys still my friends okay I'm just I'm
just telling you what the Bible said I'm
just sharing with you history one was
like we reject God because of the
hypocrisy of Christians the other was
like we accept gobble we're gonna be
hypocritical Christians so so here
happens now in America you have these
two factions one who says there must be
separation of church and state and the
other that says we the people solemnly
swear to protect and defend the
Constitution of the United States of
America so help us God are there two
warring factions in America today yet
Wow who would have thought that the
Bible accurately predicted what would
happen in America today today February
3rd 2018 we are watching these two
factions tear apart this country and
having an effect around the entire world
it is the liberal left versus the
religious right I'm just let me let me
be blown away for a moment would you
just give me a moment okay
revelation 13:12 and he exercises all
the power of the first piece before him
and cause the earth and then that draw
therein to worship the first beast whose
deadly wound was healed listen guys the
second beast the Bible says is going to
try to cause the whole world to worship
the first beast so basically what that
what that is saying is that America a
certain element in America is going to
try to return to the way things were in
the Dark Ages
how are things in the Dark Ages the
church dominated the states do you see
that do you see that happening today do
you see the Christians of today saying
we've got to turn this nation back to
God and get God back in our government
in an hour and and and it sounds good
but here's a problem you cannot use the
government to convert people the work of
conversion is only through the Holy
Spirit it is not through who you're
president is or who your political
affiliation is or who your mayor is
that's not what determines whether
America will be a Christian what will
make America a Christian nation is when
we obey the gospel and go preach to the
individual God does not want his church
married to the state seeking the state
to empower her to do her work that's not
how the Bible works and every time
church and state unite together the
result is persecution in the name of
Jesus of course because we love you and
if you don't convert we will kill you
that's not Christianity but guess what
that's what the Christian world is
saying you owe you you accept abortion
God hates you you're
God despises you you see beloved there's
a right and a wrong way to deal with
issues and everything sure that is dealt
with must be done with in love in mercy
in the character of Christ not you
listen you can personally have the horns
of a lamb yet speak like a dragon hey
brother oh okay alright how many of you
know dragon like Christians don't raise
your hand but that turns people off so
the Bible says that this first be the
second beast would seek - it would seek
to implement that which was during the
dark ages and we're seeing that unfold
right before our eyes
this first beast makes an image the
second beast makes an image - the first
piece in other words it pushes for
church and state do you see that
happening today absolutely we're
watching it before our eyes and this is
the this is absolutely mind-blowing
because revelation 13:15 says he had
power to give life unto the image of the
Beast that the image of the Beast should
both speak that's what's happening right
now this is symbolic it's not a literal
image that's going to stand up and speak
what it's saying is that an image of
something is a replica it's going to
make a replica - the first beast what
was the first piece it was a church that
ruled the States so in making an image
of this beast what it's saying is that
listen we want Christians to dominate in
politics it's the very same thing which
is going to lead to the very same
results and they cause as many as would
not worship the image of the Beast
should be killed wait a minute what not
here in America not here in America no
no no no no Christians would never do
something like that well look at the
Dark Ages don't even look at the Dark
Ages look at how angry Christians are
today
I'm talking about the religious right
look how angry they get in the name of
Jesus
think about this guys we are literally
seeing the Bible being fulfilled before
our very eyes listen just just a few
more than what the Bible predicts a
coming theocracy by misguided
hypocritical Christians in America now
in case you don't believe it let me just
let me just remind you we just spent the
last 45 minutes or so going over history
that God prophesied so if all that he
had said came to pass then what are the
odds that this will come to pass yeah
absolutely it's going to happen it's as
sure as everything we just saw can be
verified by history is as sure and
beloved you don't need to look far just
look at what is happening among the
religious right today we're not far off
out of reclaiming for at a reclaiming
America for Christ conference in
February 2005 dr. James D James Kennedy
said our job is to reclaim amassed
whatever the cost
as the Vice vice or regents of God we
are to exercise godly Dominion and
influence over our neighborhoods our
schools our government and our
literature and arts our sports arena our
entertainment media our news media our
scientific endeavors in short over every
aspect of an institution of human
society that was not the gospel
Commission guys God did not tell us
conquer your government he came to
conquer human hearts not government's
not institutions Randall Terry said this
I want you to know I want you to just
let a wave of intolerance wash over you
I want you to let a wave of hatred wash
over you yes hate is good our goal as a
Christian nation we have a biblical duty
we are called on by God to conquer this
country we don't
on equal time we don't want pluralism
that sounds pretty harsh coming from a
Christian this is called skinny
dominionism Christians have an
obligation a mandate a commission a holy
responsibility to reclaim the land for
Jesus Christ to have dominion in our
civil structures just as in every other
aspect of life and godliness but it is
demeaning we are after not just a voice
it is Dominion we're after not just
influence it is the meaning we're after
not just equal time it is Dominion we're
after world conquests
that was Christ that's what Christ has
commissioned accomplished world conquer
does that sound crazy to you world
conquest
I thought Christ commissioned his people
to make Hart conquests yep we must win
the world the world with power of the
gospel and we must never settle for
anything less
thus Christian politics has as its
primary intent the conquest of the land
of men families institutions
bureaucracies courts governments for the
kingdom of Christ Wow this this is what
drives people away from the Bible as
they look at the example Inc
Christianity is a new form of
Christianity that is spreading very
rapidly
let me just read it to you Inc leaders
have labeled them that labeled them you
see here okay
eight leaders have labeled them the
seven mountains of culture these include
business government media arts and
entertainment education family and
religion in this form of trickle-down
Christianity they believe if Christians
rise to the top of all seven mountains
society will be completely transformed
when you see people in political circles
talking about you know our conquering
for Christ this is what they're talking
about American Christianity has a plan
to conquer this government and they will
support
American Christianity has a plan to
conquer this governments and I will just
leave it there they will stop at no
means they will be will be alright with
anything in order to get their plan
accomplished which again is a definition
of hypocrisy but guess what
there's a remnant yeah even today see
when people hear about it look there are
people who you know maybe saw this
advertisement online and the first thing
they thought hypocritical Christians you
know all they want is to take over the
government not realizing guess what guys
I'm telling you in the world today there
is a small remnant of people who see and
know what you guys just learned tonight
and they are not going along with the
majority of Christians who are like us
we need to turn this nation to God they
understand that the nation is secular
they understand that god has called us
to to witness to people not to
institutions there is a remnant there is
a remnant so how is it all in who's
gonna win the religious right or the
liberal left Oh a man unfortunately it
looks like I have to end it here you
have cards if you're interested listen
listen carefully that we're last slide
here I'm gonna come back to those colors
in John 14:29
Jesus said now I have told you before it
come to pass that when it come to pass
you might what you see beloved the power
of prophecy is to us that God is real
and if he is real then we have no reason
not to believe why because when we
believe when we believe God will do some
powerful in our lives yeah before that
and like I don't know if the Bible is
real I don't know if God is real but
when you understand that God has a power
to tell the future like no one else can
have every reason to believe that he you
can trust him with your future the Bible
says where there is no vision the people
perish tonight you guys have seen the
vision God has shown you tonight what is
coming some of you it may be your first
time moving into a church and praise God
God has entrusted you with knowledge
that not a lot of have God trusted you
with this bringing you here tonight
jesus said go into all the world and
preach the gospel to every creature
that's what we're doing tonight
because we're doing that why because
when this gospel shall be preached in
all the world for a witness unto all
nations then shall the end come listen
that's my passion what I know so blew my
mind I was like I gotta tell everybody I
can and I left the industry to do that
to tell everybody I can see guys I don't
like the wool being pulled over my eyes
and I always said if I cannot explain
something to someone then I'm not gonna
I'm not gonna must get involved in it
myself
I was so convicted and convinced about
this truth I was like hey I got this I'm
ready to walk away and leave everything
I'm ready to walk away and leave
everything because you know what you
bring a skeptic you bring an atheist you
bring whoever you want to bring guess
what hey let's talk let me show you let
me show you the reason for the hope that
lies within me so you have cards for
those of you who are interested in
learning more about this all right I
want you to fill that card on and listen
I myself will personally study with you
whether it's through phone pastor what
does this mean I will study with you we
have other people who are able and
willing to study with you so all you got
to do is say hey you know what I'm
interested I'm interested I want to
learn more because there's a whole lot
more to this I want to learn more so
pastor I'm writing down my name I'm
giving you my information because I want
you to contact me because I'm interested
with that
gonna have a closing song after which we
will pray and then you will be dismissed
thank you all for coming tonight and
please listen to the words of this song
you
the theme of the Bible is Jesus and how
he died to save men the plan of
salvation assures us he's coming back
[Music]
are you ready for Jesus to come are you
faithful in all that you do
have you fought a good fight have you
stored for the right have other sin
Jesus in you are you ready to stand in
your place
are you ready to look in his face
will you look up insane
this is my
are you ready for Jesus to come
[Music]
don't cling to this world and its
treasures this earth will soon pass away
Oh give him your heart without
he's calling you to day
are you ready for Jesus to come
are you faithful
that you
have you fought a good fight have you
stood for the right have other seen
Jesus in you
are you ready to stand in your place
are you ready to look in his face
will you look up and say this is
[Music]
are you ready for Jesus
amen amen
if you have your cards and you filled
your cards I'm gonna ask if you could
just pass them down to the end of the
odds and we'll have our deacons come
around and collect those cards and then
we're gonna have a word of Prayer in
fact we'll go ahead and do that now
let's get our Deacons just coming down
the aisle just pass your cards down to
the side to the outer aisles and all
right we're not gonna do that here's
what we're gonna do as you are leaving
we're gonna have our deacons standing
right at the door
just give your car to the Deacon and and
we'll collect them from there so let's
go ahead and have a closing prayer
Heavenly Father we thank you for
speaking to us tonight we thank you for
your word we thank you for enlightening
us I pray Lord for those who are
contemplating Lord giving their lives to
you and for those who want to make a
deeper commitment lord please be with
them both and guide them is our prayer
in Jesus name Amen
god bless you thank you for coming
tonight and I'll have a good rest of
your evening